ANDREW CUDWORTH

Download as PDF

acudworth3@gmail.com

SOFTWARE ENGINEER AB-INBEV

Profile

Computer Science Master's Student graduating in August 2020. 4 years professional experience in supply chain

software implementation.

Skills React.js Data Analysis Python

Machine Learning Georgia Institute of Microsoft Excel

Technology Teradata SQL

SQL Engineering Leadership

Management Teamwork

Knime Predictive Software Analysis

Maintenance Warehouse

Management Systems

Software Testing Time Management Engineering c++ Communication Supply Chain

Operations

Microsoft Word NumPy Java

Not Afraid of Bears Tableau Supply Chain Software
Supply Chain PowerPoint Pandas (Software)
Consulting Testing Public Speaking

Microsoft Office PL/SQL Datalog

Supply Chain Matlab Reinforcement

Management Learning

Data Science HTML WMI

Oracle SQL Developer Product Development Management

Experience

Software Engineer

words

- - Azure Architecture
- - Release Engineering
- - Web App Development

2021-10-31 - present

Graduate Teaching Assistant

2019-01-31 - 2021-05-31

Course ID 6340 -Grade Assignments -Respond to Student Queries -Hold Weekly Office Hours Course Content: https://www.udacity.com/course/software-analysis-testing--ud333

Graduate Student

2018-08-31 - 2020-08-31

Business Operations Engineer

2020-10-31 - 2021-11-30

• Splunk: software defined event code based alerting and dashboarding; log analysis • Xedia Labs XLR release orchestration: automating tasks in Jenkins, Bitbucket, host SSH, BMC • IBM Mainframe to Pivotal Cloud Foundry file transfer infrastructure Migration Support

Associate Product Manager

2018-01-31 - 2018-06-30

Associate Manager Transportation Systems

2017-01-31 - 2017-12-31

Responsibilities: • Transportation Operational KPI Data specialist; deep knowledge of data sources and strategic value • Cross product and cross functional project execution via roadmap planning and direct support/implementation • Drive short and long term initiatives supporting department and company goals centered around systems/software product improvements Projects: Operational Carrier Communication Software Improvement • Centralized Real Team View of Trailer loading status UI across 15 buildings • Automate email communication process for trailer tendering via UI + UX • Minimum Viable Product rollout across 15 buildings via 6 person operational team members • Define Requirements and drive development with 1 product manager and 4 engineering associates for short and long term product requirements Operational Data Store DB KPI Migration • Coordinate KPI migration from Teradata Pull model DB to Elasticsearch Push model • Define and gather data needs for On Time Delivery and Network Transit Capability calculations • Identify data source products and partners; Ensure push from product to Elasticsearch DB • Finalize definitions and understandings for searchable Oracle Reporting DB • Document and organize transition across 5 KPI team members, 3 engineering associates and 4 product manager Cross Functional Partners: • WMT internal Order Managements Product • WMT internal Package tracking software • WMT internal Reporting DBs (Oracle, Teradata, Elasticsearch) • WMT internal Warehouse Management products +External (SSI ANT) • 6 Person transportation operational management team across 15 buildings • Walmart Labs TOPs software engineering team + Product Manager

Software Consultant

2014-08-31 - 2017-01-31

Major Projects/Clients: Americans Eagle Omni Channel Warehouse Upgrade Summary: • Supported DTC-Retail warehouse WMi system merge onsite and remote over 11 months • Upgrade from 2010 to 2013 Warehouse Management i-series code base • Coordinated with 4 member US based consulting team, 2 US based analysts and 2 India based analysts for software design, testing, installation and support for over 25 individual extensions and base code. Testing: • Tested and delivered over 25 individual software extensions on WMI-2013 platform • Created over 25 testing documents and updates extension specifications for changes made while testing • Documented base and custom configuration creating 8 specification documents for initial warehouse setup Go-Live Support • Resolved live warehouse issues on site during software testing and installation over 3 month time frame • Interfaced with client partner MHE and host vendors ensuring accuracy across 3 separate software channels • Continued issue support on and off site with project team addressing over 600 issues from testing to hand off Secondary Clients: Allen Edmonds, Polo Ralph Lauren • Testing support at peak development and delivery phases of WM-i upgrades AmerisourceBergen: Ground-Up Warehouse

Implementation June 2016-November 2016 Summary: • Acted as lead consultant on a new warehouse environment design, testing, and implementation budget >\$1M • Aligned software and process document delivery with new warehouse construction schedule • Created inventory flow and user tracking process documents for end to end warehouse process • Managed a team of 1 consultant and 1 analyst for configuration tracking and implementation Secondary Clients: Allen Edmonds, Polo Ralph Lauren Internal Trainings: SQL level ii (instructor) WMi 2015 Key Features & Additional Features, Managing your Workload with Outlook, Excel Features and Formulas: Intermediate

Engineering Intern

2013-05-31 - 2013-08-31

• Support safety analysis division with implementation of FLEX contracts • Prepare technical reports including SFPI Dosage and NRC submissions • Research EPA and NRC regulations in connection to FLEX projects • Track ENERCON progress on NRC requests for additional information Large Truck/ Diesel Generator Specification Recommendation • Recommend truck and trailer combinations for nuclear plant emergency response • Analyzed truck and generator combinations for effective towing and implementation • Communicated client needs and concerns to equipment vendors

Resident Assistant

2011-08-31 - 2013-05-31

• Manage a floor of 44 residents living in campus housing and act as a mentor and coach • Responded as first point of contact for emergencies and maintain safe living conditions

Languages

English

Native Speaker

Education

Georgia Institute of Technology Computer Science, Master's degree

Georgia Institute of Technology Mechanical Engineering, Bachelor's degree

Andrew Cudworth - acudworth3@gmail.com -